Modern Music Archives
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Iconography, 1909-1974 (Box 3-4, 8)
  - Stage and Costume Designs
    - Bennett, Robert Russell. Malibran, 1935, One reproduction (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Berg, Alban. Wozzeck (Berlin premiere), 1925, Two photo reproductions of paintings and a photo reproduction of both (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Berg, Alban. Wozzeck, 1931, One photo reproduction of painting (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Bernstein, Leonard. Facsimile, 1946, One photo reproduction of painting (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Bliss, Arthur. Adam Zero, 1946, One photograph (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Bliss, Arthur. Miracle in the Gorbals, 1944, One photograph (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Bliss, Arthur. Portraits of choreographer Robert Helpmann, Two photographs (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Blitzstein, Marc. The Cradle Will Rock, 1937, Two reproductions of three drawings (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Blitzstein, Marc. Danton's Tod, 1938, One reproduction (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Blitzstein, Marc. No for an Answer, 1940-1941, One printer's proof photo of ink etching (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Bloch, Ernest. Macbeth, 1938, Two photographs (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Brant, Henry. The Great American Goof, 1940, One sheet of costume drawings (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Britten, Benjamin. Peter Grimes, 1945, One photograph (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Britten, Benjamin. The Rape of Lucretia, undated, One photograph (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Carpenter, John. Skyscrapers, 1926, One reproduction of painting (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Chávez, Carlos. HP, 1932, One reproduction of painting by D. Rivera and one page [cast list] from 1932 program. (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Dallapiccola, Luigi. Volo di Notte, 1940, Photograph of painting (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Falla, Manuel de. El Retablo de Maese Pedro, 1926, Reproduction of drawing by R.E. Jones (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Falla, Manuel de. Three Cornered Hat, 1919, Three reproductions of drawings and painting by P. Picasso (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Gassmann, Remi. Billy Sunday, 1945, One photograph of painting by A. Calder (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Gruenberg, Louis. Emperor Jones, 1933, One reproduction of design by Mielziner (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Cardillac, 1927, Three photographs of paintings possibly by L. Pasteli; Two photographs may be from Cardillac or Mathis der Maler. (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Mathis der Maler, 1938, Two photographs of paintings by R. Clemens (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Neues vom Tage, 1927, One photograph (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Krenek, Ernst. Jonny Spielt Auf, 1929, One printer's proof (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Krenek, Ernst. Karl V, 1938, One photo reproduction of two paintings (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Krenek, Ernst. Leben des Orest, 1930, Three photographs and one sheet with reproductions of same photographs (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Malipiero, Gian Francesco. The Masque of Venice, 1932, Two printer's proof photographs of ink drawings by O. Walleck (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Malipiero, Gian Francesco. Prodigal Son, 1934, One reproduction of drawing by C. Oppo (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Menotti, Gian Carlo. The Medium, 1946, One reproduction of painting[?] by Oliver Smith (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Mignone, Francisco. Iàra, 1946, One photograph of painting by Portinari (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Milhaud, Darius. Christophe Colomb, 1930, Two printer's proof photographs and one sheet of reproductions of paintings by P. Aravantinos (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Milhaud, Darius. Les Malheurs d'Orphée, undated, Text copy and two photographs of costume designs by M.P. Hutchins (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Moore, Douglas. The Devil and Daniel Webster, 1939, One reproduction of painting by R.E. Jones (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Prokofiev, Sergei. Le Pas d'Acier, 1931, Reproductions and photographs of designs by L. Semonson (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Prokofiev, Sergei. Le Pas d'Acier, 1931, Three photographs of designs by L. Semonson (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Revueltas, Silvestre. La Coronela, 1941, One reproduced sheet of drawings by Posada (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Sauguet, Henri. La Chartreuse de Parme, 1939, One sheet of reproductions of designs by J. Dupont (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Sauguet, Henri. Fastes, 1933, Two color reproductions of designs by A. Derain (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Die Glückliche Hand, 1930, Four reproductions of designs by R.E. Jones (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Die Glückliche Hand, 1929, One reproduction of design by J. Schröder (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Pierrot Lunaire, 1930, Two reproductions of designs by R.E. Jones (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Schuman, William. Undertow, 1945, One photograph of painting by R. Breinin (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Shostakovich, Dmitri. Lady Macbeth of Mtsensk district, 1934, One photograph of painting and one reproduction of ink design by Dmitriev (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Apollon musagète, 1928, Reproduction and photograph of paintings by Bauchant (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Danses concertantes, 1944, One reproduced sheet of designs by E. Berman (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Firebird, undated, One reproduction of photograph (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. L'Histoire du Soldat, 1934, One reproduction of design by R.E. Jones (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Jeu de Cartes, 1937, One reproduction of costume design possibly by Sharaff (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Mavra, 1934, Reproductions of three designs (two sheets) by S. Soudekine (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Les Noces, 1923, Two reproductions of drawings by Gontcharova (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Les Noces, 1929, Eight reproductions of designs by S. Soudekine (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Les Noces, circa 1929, One photograph of painting by Soudekine (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Oedipus Rex, 1931, Two reproductions (one sheet) of designs by R.E. Jones (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Pulcinella, 1920, Reproduction of design by Picasso (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Le Sacre du Printemps, 1929-1930, Two photographs and two reproductions of designs by N. Roerich (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Thomson, Virgil. Filling Station, 1928, Two reproductions of designs by P. Cadnur[?] (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Thomson, Virgil. Four Saints in Three Acts, 1934, Reproduction of a photograph (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Weill, Kurt. Johnny Johnson, 1936, Reproduction of design by P. Green (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Weill, Kurt. Mahagonny, 1928, Reproduction of a photograph (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Weill, Kurt. Seven Cardinal Sins, 1933, Reproduction of design by C. Neher (Box-folder 3/20)
  - Authors and Subjects
    - 132 Modern Music photographs--introductory information by Minna Lederman (Box-folder 4/1)
    - A list of photographs in alphabetical order with explanation of classification codes and source or location information included, by Minna Lederman, Remarks in pencil by processor. (Box-folder 4/1)
    - The Modern Music photographs--suggestions for their use and display, by Minna Lederman (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Adorno, Theodor W. Photo of Adorno by Wolfgang Haut [?], undated (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Antheil, George, Hollywood, circa 1950 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Auric, Georges. Reproduction of autographed photograph of Auric, undated (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Balanchine, George. Autographed photograph from New York City Ballet, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Bartók, Béla. Two copies of Bartók photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Bauer, Marion. Reproduction of autographed photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Berg, Alban. Three photographs of Berg: one from 1935, an autographed undated one, and an 8x10 undated photograph (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Berger, Arthur. Autographed photo, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Berman, Eugene. Photograph by Man Ray, Hollywood, 1949, Autographed on verso by L. Berman. (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Bernstein, Leonard. Two photographs: one taken in 1939 and autographed in 1974, the second contains remarks and is undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Blitzstein, Marc. Two photographs: one in London, from 1942 and autographed by Blitzstein's sister Jo; the other circa 1940 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Blitzstein, Marc and Eva. Reproduction of photograph sent and autographed by Marc's sister Jo, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Boulanger, Nadia. Reproduction of autographed photo, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Bowles, Paul. Reproduction of photograph, 1950, Autographed December 28, 1973. (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Brant, Henry. Photograph with autograph attached, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Brecht, Bertolt. Testifying before House Un-American Activities Committee, 1947, Photograph by Martha Holmes Waxman. (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Breton, André. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Britten, Benjamin. Autographed photograph by Clive Strutt, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Brunswick, Mark. Photograph with original signature of his wife Natasha, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Busoni, Ferrucio. Reproduction of photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Cage, John. Photograph by Hans Namuth, circa 1969 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Carpenter, John Alden. Reproduction of photograph autographed by Ellen Carpenter (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Carter, Elliot. Autographed, 1937 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Casella, Alfredo. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Chanler, Theodore. Photograph with original signature of Yvonne Le Roux, undated (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Chávez, Carlos. One autographed photograph, Hollywood Bowl, 1937 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Citkowitz, Israel. Photograph by Alfred Stieglitz, circa 1930, Contains signature of Robert Citkowitz. (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Cocteau, Jean with Darius Milhaud. Photograph, 1922 see also Milhaud, Darius, Presented to Minna Lederman by Y. de Casa-Fuerte. (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Cocteau, Jean with Groupe des Six, Photograph from published source (Box-folder 8/6)
    - Cone, Edward T. Photograph with original autograph, circa 1970 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Cowell, Sidney Robertson. Photograph by NHK-TV, Tokyo, 1957, Contains original autograph. (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Cunningham, Merce. Photograph from The Changeling, undated (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Dahl, Ingolf. Photograph by Frank J. Thomas, 1969 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Dallapiccola, Luigi. Photograph taken in Italy, 1940 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Denby, Edwin. Photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Diamond, David. Photograph by M. Morehouse with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Einstein, Alfred. Reproduction of photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Eisler, Hans. Reproduction of photograph, 1947 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Engel, Lehman. Photograph with original autograph taken in London, undated (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Falla, Manuel de. Two different size copies of same photo, undated see also Landowska, Wanda (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Fine, Irving. Photograph taken by Harold Shapero with original signature of Verna Fine Gordon, circa 1941 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Fine, Vivian. Photograph with original autograph, circa 1940 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Foss, Lukas. Reproduction of autographed photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Frankenstein, Alfred. Photograph with original autograph, circa 1935 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Fuller, Donald. Photograph with original autograph, circa 1940 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Ginastera, Alberto. Photograph with original autograph, 1974 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Goldbeck, Eva (Blitzstein). Reproduction of photograph with signature (partially illegible), undated (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Goldman, Richard Franko. Photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Goldsmith, Dr. Alfred N. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Goossens, Eugene. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Graham, Martha. Photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Gruenberg, Louis. Photograph with original signature of Louis's wife Irma, undated (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Gutman, Hans. Photograph by Jane Rady with unidentified original signature, 1974 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Hammond, Richard. Photograph with original autograph, circa 1929 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Hanson, Howard. Photograph with original autograph by Byron Morgan, undated (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Harris, Roy. Photograph with original autograph, circa 1930s (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Harrison, Lou. Photograph by Jonathan Williams with original autograph, 1952 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Heinsheimer, Hans. Photograph with original autograph, 1932 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Henry, Leigh. Reproduction of photograph, 1931 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Herrmann, Bernard. Photograph with original autograph dated, Jan. 7, 1975 [?] (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Photograph sent by Rudolf Hindemith, 1941 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Honegger, Arthur. Photograph from early 1920s (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Hooker, Adelaide. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Ives, Charles. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Jacobi, Frederick. Photograph with original signature of D. [?] Jacobi, undated (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Jeu de Cartes three collaborators: I. Stravinsky, L. Kirstein, I. Sharaff, 1937 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Kirkpatrick, John. Photograph from the 1940s with original autograph dated Sept. 6, 1974 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Kirstein, Lincoln. Photograph from the early 1930s with original autograph from 1975 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Kodály, Zoltán. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Kolodin, Irving. Photograph with original autograph, 1936 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Krenek, Ernst. Photograph by Fritz Kempe with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Kubik, Gail. Photograph with original autograph, 1944 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Landowska, Wanda with Manuel de Falla. Photograph attached to paper with original autographs of both subjects, 1926 see also Falla, Manuel de (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Lederman, Minna. Two photographs taken for ASCAP journal article, 1937 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Lederman, Minna. Two photographs of Minna Lederman, taken for ASCAP, 1937, Black and white, 11x14 and 7x5 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Lenya, Lotte with Kurt Weill. Photograph with unidentified dedication, 1935 see also Weill, Kurt (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Lieberson, Goddard. Photograph with original autograph, circa 1930s (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Lifflander, Joel. Reproduction of 1920s photograph (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai. Photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Luening, Otto. Photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Malipiero, Gian Francesco. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Manziarly, Marcelle de. Photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/9)
    - McPhee, Colin. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Mellers, Wilfred. Photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Messiaen, Olivier. Photograph, 1946 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Milhaud, Darius. Reproduction of autographed photograph, undated see also Cocteau, Jean (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Mills, Charles. Color photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Moore, Douglas. Photograph with original signature of Sarah Moore, undated (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Moross, Jerome. Photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Morton, Lawrence. Photograph with original autograph, 1951 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Muser, Frani. Reproduction of photograph with original autograph, 1950 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Nancarrow, Conlon. Reproduction of autographed photograph, 1952 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Pisk, Paul A. Photograph with original autograph, 1936 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Piston, Walter. Photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Porter, Quincy. Reproduction of autographed photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Prokofiev, Sergei. Photograph, early 1920s (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Ravel, Maurice. Reproduction of "early photo," undated (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Reis, Claire. Photograph by David Berns, 1930 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Revueltas, Silvestre. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Rogers, Bernard. Matted photograph with original signature of his wife Elizabeth C. Rogers, 1946 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Rosenfeld, Paul. Photograph by Alfred Stieglitz, undated (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Ruggles, Carl. Reproduction of autographed photograph, 1961 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Russian composers: individual photos of Khatchaturian, Khrennikov, Miaskovsky, Mossolov and Tchemodanov, undated (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Saminsky, Lazare. Reproduction of autographed photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Sanborn, Pitts. Reproduction of photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Satie, Erik. Photograph by Brancusi, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Sauguet, Henri. Photograph by P. Leclerc with original autograph, 1974 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Schoenberg studio. Press release photograph of studio replica at Schoenberg Institute at USC, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Schuman, William. One matted and autographed black and white photograph, 1971 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Scriabin, Aleksandr. Reproduction of photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Searle, Humphrey. Reproduction of autographed photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Seeger, Charles. Color photograph by Simpson, 1973, Signed by Jean [?] Seeger, 1974. (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Seeger, Ruth Crawford. Photograph with original signature of Charles Seeger, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Seldes, Gilbert. Photograph with original signature of daughter Marian Seldes, 1932 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Sessions, Roger. Reproduction of photograph with original autograph, late 1920s (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Shapero, Harold. Photograph with original autograph, March 1974 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Shostakovich, Dmitri. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Slonimsky, Nicolas. Photograph with original autograph, 1974 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Smallens, Alexander. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Stein, Erwin. Photograph by Roger Wood, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Reproduction of autographed photograph, 1945 see also Jeu de Cartes three collaborators, Autograph from 1948. (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Stuckenschmidt, H. H. Photograph by Nina von Jaanson with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Tailleferre, Germaine. Photograph with original autograph, early 1920s (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Talma, Louise. Photograph with original autograph, March 1947 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Taylor, Davidson. Photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Thompson, Randall. Two photographs: one from the 1930s; the other with original autograph, 1973, The autograph from 1974. (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Thomson, Virgil. Two photographs: one by Harry Dunham with original autograph dated 1936; the other dated 1941 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Varèse, Edgard. Photograph with original signature of Louise Varèse, undated (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Varèse, Louise. Photograph by Stephanie Rancou with original autograph, 1970s (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Villa-Lobos, Heitor, undated (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Ward, Robert. Photograph with original autograph, undated (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Webern, Anton. One photograph, undated (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Weill, Kurt. Photograph with original signature of Lotte Lenya see also Lenya, Lotte (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Weiss, Adolf. Photograph by Alfred Carlson with original signature of sister Mildred Baker, undated (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Wigman, Mary. Reproduction of autographed photograph, 1952 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Wolpe, Stefan, Photograph missing as of February 1993. (Box-folder 4/13)
- Scrapbooks, 1924-1947 (Box 5-6)
  - Modern Music promotion book, 1924-1946, Scrapbook with green cover with gold accents; 56 p.; Contains materials used in promotion, advertising and subscription services. All materials are the work of Joel Lifflander, long-time volunteer and technical director at Modern Music. (Box 5)
  - Modern Music press book, 1925-1947, Scrapbook with black cover; 94 p.; Contains press clippings concerning Modern Music, its contributors and reprints of articles. (Box 6)
- Auxiliary Pamphlets, 1925-1938 (Box 7)
  - Auxiliary Pamphlets - General information by Minna Lederman (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Program from German Staatsoper for production of Berg's Wozzeck, Dec. 1925, 24 p. (Box-folder 7/2)
  - Neue Musik-Zeitung, July 1926, 28 p. (Box-folder 7/3)
  - Program from Deutsche Kammermusik Baden Baden, 25-28 Juli, 1929, 28 p. (Box-folder 7/4)
  - Program from Carlos Chávez's H.P. (Caballos de vapor), the world premiere at Philadelphia Grand Opera Company, Mar. 1932, 8 p.; This item is not mentioned in Minna Lederman's "General Information" regarding auxiliary pamphlets. (Box-folder 7/5)
  - Libretto for Shostakovich's Lady Macbeth of the Mtsensk district or Katerina Izmaǐlova. By Aleksandr Preǐs. Published by A.S. Gilman Co., Cleveland, OH, 1935, 24 p. (Box-folder 7/6)
  - Entartete Musik: eine Abrechnung von Staatsrat Dr. Hans Severus Ziegler. Published by Völkischer Verlag, Düsseldorf, 1938, 32 p.; Laid in: newspaper clipping from Musical America, July 1938, titled "Düsseldorf Exhibits 'Degenerate Music'," written by Geraldine De Courcy. (Box-folder 7/7)
- Supplemental Material, 1924-1946 (Box 7)
  - Additional material: List of items added to collection after completion of inventory, 2 p. (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Index: Volumes I - XII, November 1924 to June 1935. Published by The League of Composers, Nov. 1935, 63 p. (Box-folder 7/9)
  - Reich, Dr. Willi; translated by Adolph Weiss. A Guide to Alban Berg's Opera Wozzeck, 1931, Modern Music Monographs. Published by The League of Composers. (Box-folder 7/10)
  - Final issue of Modern Music, Volume XXIII, No. 4, Fall 1946, 336 p. (Box-folder 7/11)
  - First issue of The League of Composers' Review, Vol I, no. 1, Feb. 1924, 28 p.; Published by the League of Composers, Inc., New York, NY. (Box-folder 7/12)
- Oversize Iconography, 1928, 1934
  Housed in the vault.
  - A color lithograph (unframed) of Paul Hindemith by Richard Heinsich, 1934
  - Original pen and ink drawing of Sergei Prokofiev by Natalia Gontcharova, 1928